

<u> astridavalin@gmail.com</u>

Q Rytterparken 74, Hornslet, 8543, Denmark

|    | +4526 |  |
|----|-------|--|
|    |       |  |
| ¢. |       |  |

# **Details**

Driving license Nationality
Yes (B) Danish

## **Profile**

**Ambitious Software Engineer** (and dedicated cat mom) with 9 years of coding experience and a passion for clean, purposeful code. Experienced in agile teams using SCRUM, with a strong eye for detail and code quality. I apply SMART principles not just in planning, but in every implementation decision - striving for solutions that are specific, measurable, achievable, relevant, and testable

## Skills

| C#               | INET           |  |
|------------------|----------------|--|
| Unity            | Java           |  |
| Git              | Github Actions |  |
| CI/CD            | Autodesk Maya  |  |
| Autodesk 3ds Max | Blender        |  |
| Python           | HTML & CSS     |  |
| SQL              | RESTful        |  |
| JavaScript       | Node.js        |  |
| C++              | Lua            |  |

# **Professional Experience**

## Software Pilot, Trifork, Århus

March 2021 — December 2024

- Developed the LEGO Super Mario app, while gaining understanding of Jira, Confluence, and CI/CD with GitLab. The app communicated with multiple Bluetooth devices, and this was handled using pure C#.
- Built an iOS app from scratch to open and close windows internally on location with Swift as
  frontend & WebSockets as the communication layer. I also delved deeply into building full
  CI/CD pipelines with YAML via Github Actions.
- Developer on the virtual Fish Designer experience at LEGO House with a focus on Unity/C# tasks. All code was written with MVP architecture in mind.

 Contributed to creating a demo VR flight training app for Apple Vision Pro, aiming to handle in-flight emergencies. The application was written in Unity/C#

#### Unity Developer, AquaGlobe, Skanderborg

February 2019 — June 2019

- Worked together with an amazing colleague, creating an XR app for Microsoft HoloLens to tour different water facilities.
- Mediator between different firms on the possibilities with this relatively new hardware, to create a mutual vision.
- Creating simple 3D models in Maya to illustrate some of the machines at the facility
- Read more about the experience here

#### **R&D Backend Developer, Smartplan, Arhus**

August 2017 — December 2017

- Internship started at Smartplan, and was introduced to a R&D environment.
- Here, I created the backend for an automated rostering tool using Java and Optaplanner (Drools Rule Engine) from scratch.
- After the internship ended, I was hired to finish and polish the tool.

## Education

#### Software Engineer, VIA University College, Viborg

August 2018 — January 2021

I got a bachelor in Software Engineering with a specialization in AR & VR. I got familiar with developing for a lot of different HMDs from Microsoft HoloLens (XR), Oculus Rift/Quest & HTC Vive.

## Computer Science AP Degree, Erhvervsakademi Aarhus, Århus

August 2015 — May 2018

I finished an AP degree in computer science, where I have specialized in mobile development. I got a bunch of my general tools during this education and a great foundation of my coding knowledge.

#### Math A Degree, VUC, Arhus

June 2014 — June 2015

In order to continue my studies with computer science, I needed to increase my math from C-level to A-level, and thus I spent a year on VUC to achieve that.

#### High School Diploma, Egå Gymnasium, Egå

August 2011 — May 2014

I specialized within the creative line, which means I had Music & English on A-level and Drama on C-level. This also means I am pretty familiar with a ukulele and piano by now.

## Languages

| Danish | English |  |
|--------|---------|--|
|        |         |  |

#### **Hobbies**

Creating, modding and playing video games. Furthermore I enjoy drawing pixel art, playing ukulele and skateboarding.

#### Links

My portfolio

#### References

References available upon request